planetozkids.com 2018-12-16

# Privacy Policy - Planet Ozkids - A world of learning, fun and games for kids

The policies below are applicable to Ozkids.com and Planet Ozkkids.com and other sites on the Internet owned and operated by Word Design Interactive Pty. Ltd.

#### The Legal Stuff

By using our website, you confirm that you agree to our terms and conditions of use and the terms of our privacy policy, described below. We also reserve the right, at our soul discretion, to make additions, deletions, or other changes to our terms of use and privacy policy at any time. It is your responsibility to periodically check these terms for any changes. Continuing to use Planet Ozkids On-line following the publishing of these changes means you accept the changes. 

Sorry about all the legal stuff but we have to protect our copyrighted material – and most importantly, keep our website fun and safe to use for the kids and their parents and teachers visiting this site.

#### Privacy Policy

We recognise that parents are concerned about the privacy of their family and especially the privacy of their children on-line.

We do not require personal information from visitors before allowing them to access any part of our website. Any requests for data are entirely voluntary. 

We are trying to bring you the best on-line experience possible so we may ask visitors to share information or submit details to register for newsletters or enter competitions or to help us improve the site.  Children under 18 should always seek permission from their parents or guardian before transmitting any information. 

We are totally committed to the privacy of this information and will under no circumstance release, sell, share or transfer information to third parties. 

As we add more features and services to our site for your benefit and new laws regarding the use of the Internet occur, we may have to update this privacy policy. Rest assured we do not anticipate changing from our philosophy of protecting the privacy of visitors to this site or using in an inappropriate way information disclosed to us.

#### Visitor Tracking

We do use software to track the total number of visitors to our site and the number of visitors to each area of the site.  This information only shows us which areas visitors enjoy most and helps us to improve the site.  We do not extract personal information in this process. This means the user remains anonymous to us.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

#### Use of Site 

By using this site, you signify your assent to the Word Design Interactive Pty. Ltd. Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. 

Please also read our Terms and Conditions of Use.

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us.

Bob Smith  
Planet Ozkids
